Press Gang Printers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Correspondence and subject files, 1970 - 1992; F-134-4; 52 cm of textual records
  - Country Women (magazine), 1975 - 1976; F-134-4-0-0-25 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Country Women, vol. 21, September 1976; F-134-4-0-0-25-2 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item18.
  - Energy file (newsletter), 1979; F-134-4-0-0-26 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - The Energy File, vol. 2 no. 1, February 1979; F-134-4-0-0-26-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item19.
    - The Energy File, vol. 2 no. 2, March 1979; F-134-4-0-0-26-2 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item20.
    - The Energy File, vol. 2 no. 4, May 1979; F-134-4-0-0-26-3 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item21.
    - The Energy File, vol. 2 no. 6, August 1979; F-134-4-0-0-26-4 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item22.
  - Fed-Up: The Catalist (newsletter), 1976; F-134-4-0-0-27 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Fed Up: The Catalist, vol. 2 no. 5, August 1976; F-134-4-0-0-27-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item23.
    - Fed Up: The Catalist, vol. 2 no. 6, October 1976; F-134-4-0-0-27-2 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item24.
    - Fed Up: The Catalist, vol. 2 no. 8, December 1976; F-134-4-0-0-27-3 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item25.
  - Feminist Art Journal, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 134-10)
  - Feminist News Service, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-29 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Feminist News Service, vol. 1 no. 4, September 1975; F-134-4-0-0-29-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item26.
  - Feminist Party of Canada News, 1979 - 1980; F-134-4-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 134-10)
  - General, 1989 - 1991; F-134-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 134-10)
  - Georgia Straight (newspaper), 1976; F-134-4-0-0-32 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - The Georgia Straight, vol. 10 no. 453, July 1976; F-134-4-0-0-32-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item27.
    - The Women's Liberated Georgia Straight, vol. 1 no. 1, April [197-?]; F-134-4-0-0-32-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item28.
  - Guelph Women's Centre: Virgago (newsletter), 1974 - 1975; F-134-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 134-10)
  - Homosexuality, 1976; F-134-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Hysteria (magazine), 1981 - 1985; F-134-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Infant Formula Action Committee: INFACT (newsletter), 1977; F-134-4-0-0-36 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Infant Formula Action Coalition (INFACT), 1977; F-134-4-0-0-36-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item29.
  - International Women's Day, 1977; F-134-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
    Reviewed for access (Dec 6, 2023) – File includes records that contain some individuals' personal contact information. File can be accessed in the Archives' reading room, but will be redacted in any digital access copies made by Archives.
  - Kitchener-Waterloo Women's Place: Building the Movement From One Women's Centre to Another, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-38 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Kitchener-Waterloo Women's Place: Building the Movement, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-38-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item30.
  - Kite: Anti-Prison News Journal, 1979; F-134-4-0-0-39 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - The Kite: Anti-prison Newsjournal, 1979; F-134-4-0-0-39-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item31.
  - Leftwords (newspaper), 1979 - 1983; F-134-4-0-0-40 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Leftwords, vol. 1 no. 4, August 1979; F-134-4-0-0-40-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item33.
    - Leftwords, vol. 1 no. 5, October 1979; F-134-4-0-0-40-2 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item34.
    - Leftwords, vol. 1 no. 7, December 1979; F-134-4-0-0-40-3 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item35.
    - Leftwords, vol. 1 no. 8, February 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-4 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item36.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 2, May 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-5 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item37.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 3, June 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-6 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item38.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 3, June 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-7 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item39.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 4, July 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-8 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item40.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 5, September 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-9 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item41.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 7, December 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-10 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item42.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 7, December 1980; F-134-4-0-0-40-11 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item43.
    - Leftwords, vol. 2 no. 9, March 1981; F-134-4-0-0-40-12 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item44.
    - Leftwords, vol. 3 no. 1, April 1981; F-134-4-0-0-40-13 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item45.
    - Leftwords, vol. 3 no. 2, May 1981; F-134-4-0-0-40-14 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item46.
    - Leftwords, vol. 3 no. 3, June 1981; F-134-4-0-0-40-15 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item47.
    - Leftwords, vol. 3 no. 4, October 1981; F-134-4-0-0-40-16 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item48.
    - Leftwords, vol. 3 no. 6, December 1981; F-134-4-0-0-40-17 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item49.
    - Leftwords, vol. 4 no. 1, April 1982; F-134-4-0-0-40-18 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item50.
    - Leftwords, vol. 4 no. 2, May 1982; F-134-4-0-0-40-19 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item51.
    - Leftwords, vol. 4 no. 4, August 1982; F-134-4-0-0-40-20 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item52.
    - Leftwords, vol. 4 no. 5, April 1983; F-134-4-0-0-40-21 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item53.
  - Leonard Peltier Defence Committee, 1977; F-134-4-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Lesbian Connection (magazine), 1977; F-134-4-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Lesbian / Lesbienne (magazine), 1981; F-134-4-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Lesbian Tide (newspaper), 1977; F-134-4-0-0-44 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Lesbian Tide, vol. 7 no. 1, July 1977; F-134-4-0-0-44-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item54.
  - Lesbianism, 1977 - 1981; F-134-4-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 134-10)
  - Letters of support - incoming, 1978 - 1980; F-134-4-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 134-10)
  - Letters of support - outgoing, 1978 - 1982; F-134-4-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 134-10)
  - Letters of support - outgoing, 1980 - 1982; F-134-4-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Makara - incorporation papers, minutes, correspondence, 1979 - 1981; F-134-4-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Manchester Women's Paper, 1977; F-134-4-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Matrix (newspaper), 1980; F-134-4-0-0-51 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Matrix, vol. 1 no. 9, April 1980; F-134-4-0-0-51-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item55.
  - Mental health - State and Mind (magazine), 1977 - 1978; F-134-4-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Momentum (newspaper), 1971; F-134-4-0-0-53 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Momentum, vol. 1, January 1971; F-134-4-0-0-53-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item56.
    - Momentum, vol. 3, March 1971; F-134-4-0-0-53-2 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item57.
  - Montreal Power of Women Collective, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Native people, 1981; F-134-4-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - New Directions for Women (newspaper), 1979 - 1982; F-134-4-0-0-56 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - New Directions for Women, vol. 8 no. 4, 1979; F-134-4-0-0-56-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item58.
    - New Directions for Women, vol. 11 no. 6, November 1982; F-134-4-0-0-56-2 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item59.
  - New Women's Times (magazine), 1979 - 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - New Women's Times, vol. 5 no. 10, May 1979; F-134-4-0-0-57-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item60.
    - New Women's Times, vol. 8 no. 6, June 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item61.
    - New Women's Times, vol. 8 no. 7, July 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item62.
    - New Women's Times, vol. 8 no. 9, October 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-4 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item63.
    - New Women's Times, vol. 8 no. 10, November 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-5 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item64.
    - New Women's Times, vol. 8 no. 11, December 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-6 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item65.
    - New Women's Times, December 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-7 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item66.
    - New Women's Times - Feminist Review no. 22, July 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-8 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item67.
    - New Women's Times - Feminist Review no. 23, September 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-9 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item68.
    - New Women's Times - Feminist Review no. 24, November 1982; F-134-4-0-0-57-10 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item69.
  - Ochiltree Commune (Williams Lake): In Defence of Nature (newspaper), 1978; F-134-4-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Other Woman (newspaper), 1975 - 1976; F-134-4-0-0-59 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - The Other Woman, vol. 3 no. 4, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-59-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item70.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 4 no. 6, November 1976; F-134-4-0-0-59-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item71.
  - Our Own Older Women's Network, 1978; F-134-4-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Out of Line (newspaper), 1986; F-134-4-0-0-61 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Out of Line, vol. 1 no. 19, July 1986; F-134-4-0-0-61-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item72.
  - Paid My Dues: Quarterly Journal of Wmen and Music, 1974; F-134-4-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Partisan (newspaper), 1971; F-134-4-0-0-63 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Partisan, August 1971; F-134-4-0-0-63-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item73.
  - Plexus: San Francisco - Bay Area Women's Newspaper, 1983; F-134-4-0-0-64 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Plexus: San Fransisco Bay Area Women's Newspaper, vol. 10 no. 2, April 1983; F-134-4-0-0-64-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item74.
  - Political statements by various groups, 1978 - 1980; F-134-4-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Port Coquitlam Area Women's Centre: Intercom bulletin, 1976; F-134-4-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Prairie Woman (newspaper), 1977 - 1981; F-134-4-0-0-67 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 1 no. 4, October 1977; F-134-4-0-0-67-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item75.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 1 no. 6, December 1977; F-134-4-0-0-67-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item76.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 1, January 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item77.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 3, March 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-4 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item78.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 4, April 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-5 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item79.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 5, May 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-6 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item80.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 6, July 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-7 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item81.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 7, September 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-8 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item82.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 8, October 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-9 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item83.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 8, December 1978; F-134-4-0-0-67-10 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item84.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 2 no. 9, February 1979; F-134-4-0-0-67-11 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item85.
    - Prairie Woman, August 1979; F-134-4-0-0-67-12 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item86.
    - Prairie Woman, vol. 3 no. 4, October 1979; F-134-4-0-0-67-13 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item87.
    - Prairie Woman, January 1980; F-134-4-0-0-67-14 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item88.
    - Prairie Woman, May 1980; F-134-4-0-0-67-15 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item89.
    - Prairie Woman, October 1980; F-134-4-0-0-67-16 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item90.
    - Prairie Woman, January 1981; F-134-4-0-0-67-17 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item91.
  - Press Gang Publishers Collective - correspondence, 1987 - 1989; F-134-4-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Prison (newspaper), 1979; F-134-4-0-0-69 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Prison, vol. 1 no. 4, 1979; F-134-4-0-0-69-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item92.
  - Prisoners Union Investigation Committee, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-70 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Prisoner's Union Committee Investigation, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-70-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item93.
  - Progressive Printers, 1985 - 1992; F-134-4-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Protest letters, 1976 - 1982; F-134-4-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
    Reviewed for access (Dec 12, 2023) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (2) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (medical/psychological history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
  - Quebec, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-73 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Free Quebec, vol. 1, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-73-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item94.
    - Free Quebec, vol. 2, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-73-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item95.
    - Free Quebec, vol. 3, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-73-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item96.
    - Free Quebec, vol. 2, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-73-4 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item97.
    - Free Quebec, vol. 3, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-73-5 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item98.
  - Second Wave (magazine), 1973 - 1975; F-134-4-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Security, [197-?]; F-134-4-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Service, Office, and Retail Workers Union of Canada (SORWUC), 1976 - 1977; F-134-4-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 134-11)
  - Service, Office, and Retail Workers Union of Canada (SORWUC) - minutes, 1977 - 1978; F-134-4-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Shocking Pink (magazine), 1980; F-134-4-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Sister: West Coast Feminist Newspaper, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-79 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Sister: Westcoast Feminist Newspaper, August 1975; F-134-4-0-0-79-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item99.
  - Socred budget cuts, 1976; F-134-4-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Solidarity Times (newspaper), 1983; F-134-4-0-0-81 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Solidarity Times, vol. 1 no. 3, November 1983; F-134-4-0-0-81-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item100.
    - Solidarity Times, vol. 1 no. 4, November 1983; F-134-4-0-0-81-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item101.
    - Solidarity Times, vol. 1 no. 4, November 1983; F-134-4-0-0-81-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item102.
  - Solitary Confinement Project, 1978; F-134-4-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Songs I Learned at My Mother's Knees, 1976; F-134-4-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Spare Change (newspaper), 1971; F-134-4-0-0-84 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Spare Change no. 2, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-84-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item103.
    - Spare Change no. 2, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-84-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item104.
  - Spare Rib (magazine), 1980; F-134-4-0-0-85 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Spare Rib, vol. 100, November 1980; F-134-4-0-0-85-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item105.
  - Statistics Canada survey of manufacturers, 1990; F-134-4-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Thank you letters and testimonials, 1991 - 1992; F-134-4-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Through the Looking Glass: A Women's and Children's Prison Newsletter, [197-?]; F-134-4-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Unions, vol. 1, 1975 - 1982; F-134-4-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Unions, vol. 2, 1975 - 1982; F-134-4-0-0-90 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 2 no. 5, May 1975; F-134-4-0-0-90-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item106.
    - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 2 no. 7, August 1975; F-134-4-0-0-90-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item107.
    - The Housewife, November 1970; F-134-4-0-0-90-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item108.
    - Negotiations no. 3, March 1981; F-134-4-0-0-90-4 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item109.
    - Gatt-fly, August 1978; F-134-4-0-0-90-5 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item110.
    - S.O.R.W.U.C. News, vol. 1 no. 1, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-90-6 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item111.
    - Focus: The Working Paper for Working People, vol. 2 no. 5, June 1977; F-134-4-0-0-90-7 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item112.
  - United Church of Canada: Working Women, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-91 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Working Women: United Church of Canada no. 6, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-91-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item113.
  - Upstream (newspaper), 1978; F-134-4-0-0-92 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Upstream, April 1978; F-134-4-0-0-92-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item114.
  - Vancouver Resources Board, 1977; F-134-4-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Vancouver Worker (newspaper), 1971; F-134-4-0-0-94 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Vancouver Worker, vol. 1 no. 3, August 1971; F-134-4-0-0-94-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item115.
  - Victoria Faulkner Women's Centre, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-95 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Victoria Faulkner Women's Centre no. 8, 1975; F-134-4-0-0-95-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item116.
  - Wages for Housework, 1976; F-134-4-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Wages for Housework Campaign Bulletin, 1978; F-134-4-0-0-97 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Wages for Housework Campaign Bulletin, vol. 3 no. 1, 1978; F-134-4-0-0-97-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item117.
  - Weather Underground: The Symbionese Guerillas, 1974; F-134-4-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Western Canadian Women's News Service, vol. 1, 1974 - 1976; F-134-4-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Western Canadian Women's News Service, vol. 2, 1974 - 1976; F-134-4-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women: A Journal of Liberation, 1971; F-134-4-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women Against Electric Shock Treatment, [197-?]; F-134-4-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women Against Rape, 1977; F-134-4-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
    Open, no restrictions
    Reviewed for access (Nov 23, 2023) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
  - Women in Print - 3rd National Conference, 1984 - 1985; F-134-4-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women Now! (magazine), 1971; F-134-4-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women's Collective Press (newspaper), 1975; F-134-4-0-0-106 (Newspaper box 134-30)